<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Clay&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://claygardner.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Clay&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://claygardner.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pillars Of A Good Hire</title>
      <link>https://claygardner.io/blog/pillars-of-a-good-hire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claygardner.io/blog/pillars-of-a-good-hire/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to break into the tech industry? Get out of that mindless software contracting job? This guide is for you!
Recently I was stuck in a dead end government contracting job&amp;ndash;my first out of college. I decided that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for me and made a plan of attack to break into a far more challenging and rewarding position. These are the three pillars I based my preparation on that lead to multiple offers&amp;ndash;including one that doubled my previous base salary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using API Gateway with Content Type other than JSON</title>
      <link>https://claygardner.io/blog/api-gateway-any-content-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 15:00:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claygardner.io/blog/api-gateway-any-content-type/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; API Gateway and Lambda are perfect for capturing webhooks. The only problem is when the webhook being captured uses something other than application/json as the content-type. Webhooks, or any type of request passing a payload, cannot deliver their data without some changes to your API Gateway.
Let&amp;rsquo;s create a API Gateway endpoint that takes application/x-www-form-urlencoded and returns the same data formatted in application/json. The easiest way to do this is set up a lambda function as our backend that consumes and processes our raw data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>